<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<!-- <!DOCTYPE ead PUBLIC "+//ISBN 1-931666-00-8//DTD ead.dtd (Encoded Archival Description (EAD) Version 2002)//EN" "http://lcweb2.loc.gov/xmlcommon/dtds/ead2002/ead.dtd" [ <!ENTITY uwmlogo SYSTEM "foo.jpg" NDATA jpeg>] > -->
<ead id="uw-mil-uwmac0221" relatedencoding="MARC21">
	<eadheader langencoding="iso639-2b" audience="internal" countryencoding="iso3166-1"
		dateencoding="iso8601" repositoryencoding="iso15511" scriptencoding="iso15924"
		relatedencoding="MARC21">
		<eadid encodinganalog="856$u" countrycode="us" mainagencycode="wimiugma"
			url="http://digital.library.wisc.edu/1711.dl/wiarchives.uw-mil-uwmac0221"
			>uw-mil-uwmac0221</eadid>
		<filedesc>
			<titlestmt>
				<titleproper encodinganalog="245$a">Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Web Collection,
					1997-2017</titleproper>
				<author encodinganalog="245$c">Brad Houston</author>
			</titlestmt>
			<publicationstmt>
				<publisher encodinganalog="260$b">University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries,
					Archives Department</publisher>
				<address>
					<addressline>University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee</addressline>
					<addressline>UWM Libraries</addressline>
					<addressline>Archives Department</addressline>
					<addressline>P.O. Box 604</addressline>
					<addressline>Milwaukee, Wisconsin 53201-0604</addressline>
					<addressline>URL: www.uwm.edu/Libraries/arch/index.html<extptr href="http://www.uwm.edu/Libraries/arch/index.html"/></addressline>
				</address>
				<date encodinganalog="260$c" type="publication" normal="2012">Copyright &#169; 2013
					University of Wisconsin Board of Regents</date>
			</publicationstmt>
		</filedesc>
		<profiledesc>
			<creation encodinganalog="500">Finding aid encoded by Brad Houston.</creation>
			<langusage encodinganalog="546">Finding aid written in <language encodinganalog="041"
					langcode="eng" scriptcode="Latn">English.</language></langusage>
		</profiledesc>
		<revisiondesc>
			<change>
				<date normal="2017-03-28">March 28, 2017</date>
				<item>Brad Houston updated the finding aid to reflect the addition of new pages and
					sites to the collection, in conjunction with a 2017 Alternate Spring Break
					project. Changes were made to extent, accessioninfo, processinfo, scopecontent,
					relatedmaterial, and the contents list.</item>
			</change>
			<change>
				<date normal="2014-05-14">May 14, 2014</date>
				<item>Brad Houston made some formatting changes to the contents list.</item>
			</change>
			<change>
				<date normal="2014-05-07">May 7, 2014</date>
				<item>Charles Tonelli updated the finding aid to reflect the addition of new pages
					and sites to the collection. Changes were made to processinfo and the contents
					list.</item>
			</change>
			<change>
				<date normal="2013-03-28">March 28, 2013</date>
				<item>Brad Houston updated the finding aid to reflect the addition of new pages and
					sites to the collection. Changes were made to physdesc, accessioninfo,
					processinfo, and the contents list.</item>
			</change>
		</revisiondesc>
	</eadheader>
	<archdesc level="collection" relatedencoding="MARC21">
		<did>
			<physloc type="locationcode" audience="internal">wimiugma</physloc>
			<unittitle encodinganalog="245$a">UW-Milwaukee Web Collection, <unitdate
					type="inclusive" encodinganalog="245$f" normal="1997/2017"
				>1997-2017</unitdate></unittitle>
			<origination label="Creator">
				<corpname encodinganalog="110">University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee</corpname>
			</origination>
			<unitid label="Call Number" encodinganalog="099" repositorycode="us-wimiugma"
				countrycode="us">UWM Archival Collection 221</unitid>
			<physdesc label="Quantity">
				<extent encodinganalog="300">Approximately 6 million digital files (414 GB)</extent>
			</physdesc>
			<repository encodinganalog="852">
				<extptr entityref="uwmlogo" show="embed" actuate="onload" altrender="center"
					title="University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Logo." role="logoimage"/>
				<extref href="http://www.uwm.edu/Libraries/arch/index.html">
					<corpname>University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives
						Department</corpname>
				</extref>
			</repository>
			<physloc/>
			<abstract encodinganalog="520">Web collection of University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee
				websites and affiliated sites crawled by the UWM Libraries, Archives Department
				using the Internet Archive's Archive-It web crawler beginning in 2012, as well as
				pages crawled by the Internet Archive from 1997 to 2017. The web collection includes
				websites, blogs, Facebook pages, Flickr pages, and Twitter feeds created by various
				divisions, offices, and departments of the University of
				Wisconsin-Milwaukee.</abstract>
			<langmaterial encodinganalog="546" label="Language">
				<language encodinganalog="041" langcode="eng">English</language>
			</langmaterial>
		</did>
		<scopecontent encodinganalog="520">
			<p>Official websites, social media accounts, and affiliated sites relating to the
				University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee. The collection was initially captured using the
				Internet Archive's Archive-It Web Crawler between October 2012 and January 2013, and
				updated periodically thereafter. The collection contains websites, Facebook pages,
				Twitter accounts, Flickr accounts, and other web content created by offices and
				divisions of the University. Most of the official pages and documents captured are
				hosted on the uwm.edu server, though some are housed on other subdomains and are
				listed separately. In addition to the UWM homepage, homepages and sub-sites for each
				of the University's divisions, schools, and colleges are listed separately for ease
				of access.</p>
			<p>Full text search of web collection and browsing of the collection's videos are
				available at the <extref actuate="onrequest" show="new"
					href="http://archive-it.org/collections/3368">collection landing page</extref>
				on the Archive-It site. See the entries for individual sites for additional
				information about the scope and content of each site.</p>
			<p>Some entries will have links to multiple instances of their website. In most of these
				cases, these links indicate either that the site URL has changed dramatically, or
				that the Internet Archive Wayback Machine captured the page before UWM began
				crawling its site in 2012. The latter case is indicated as "Internet Archive
				Capture." Note that the Internet Archive captures typically only capture the first
				few levels of a given website; for more in-depth captures, please refer to the
				Archive-It capture.</p>
			<p>Beginning in 2015, the UWM Archives began adding metadata points to key series on the
				UWM Website, including meeting minutes, Faculty Senate documents, policies and
				procedures, and publications landing pages. Where possible, links to such entry
				points are accessible through the finding aid of the parent collection. The contents
				list for this collection only lists the primary "seeds" or starting points for the
				web crawler.</p>
		</scopecontent>
		<arrangement encodinganalog="351">
			<p>The base unit of description is school, division, or office website, subdomain, or
				social media account. The collection is arranged into six functional series:</p>
			<list numeration="arabic" type="ordered">
				<item>
					<ref target="series1" show="replace" actuate="onrequest">Main Site,
						1997-2017</ref>
				</item>
				<item>
					<ref target="series2" show="replace" actuate="onrequest">Academic and Research
						Units, 1997-2017</ref>
				</item>
				<item>
					<ref target="series3" show="replace" actuate="onrequest">Administrative Units,
						1997-2017</ref>
				</item>
				<item>
					<ref target="series4" show="replace" actuate="onrequest">Athletics,
						2000-2017</ref>
				</item>
				<item>
					<ref target="series5" show="replace" actuate="onrequest">Social Media,
						2009-2017</ref>
				</item>
				<item>
					<ref target="series6" show="replace" actuate="onrequest">Affiliate Sites,
						2012-2017</ref>
				</item>
			</list>
		</arrangement>
		<otherfindaid encodinganalog="555">
			<p><extref actuate="onrequest" show="new" href="https://archive-it.org/collections/3368"
					>The Archive-It landing page for the collection</extref> includes more
				information about the materials in the collection, including site-specific and
				document-specific metadata and exact dates of capture.</p>
		</otherfindaid>
		<prefercite encodinganalog="524">
			<p>
				<extref
					href="http://uwm.edu/libraries/archives/research/citation-guide-for-primary-sources/"
					>Citation Guide for Primary Sources</extref>
			</p>
		</prefercite>
		<descgrp type="admininfo">
			<head>Administrative/Restriction Information</head>
			<accessrestrict encodinganalog="506">
				<p>There are no access restrictions on the materials, and the collection is open to
					all members of the public in accordance with state law.</p>
			</accessrestrict>
			<userestrict encodinganalog="540">
				<p>The researcher assumes full responsibility for conforming with the laws of libel,
					privacy, and copyright which may be involved in the use of this collection
					(Wisconsin Statutes 19.21-19.39).</p>
			</userestrict>
			<acqinfo encodinganalog="541">
				<p>The initial materials were collected by the UWM Archives between October 2012 and
					January 2013, using Internet Archive's Archive-It web capture service.
					Archive-It used the Heritrix web crawler to capture and archive web pages. Brad
					Houston ran new crawls in March and November of 2013, 2014, 2015, 2016, and in
					March of 2017 to add additional pages and sites to the collection.</p>
			</acqinfo>
			<processinfo encodinganalog="583">
				<p>Brad Houston and Charles Welborn processed the initial collection in winter 2013.
					Brad Houston processed the added materials in March 2013. Grant Roedl updated
					the finding aid to reflect new seeds and updated metadata on the Archive-It site
					as part of a SOIS Alternative Spring Break project in March 2017 (Brad Houston
					supervised).</p>
			</processinfo>
		</descgrp>
		<dsc type="in-depth">
			<head>Contents List</head>
			<c01 id="series1" level="series">
				<did>
					<unittitle>1. Main Website, <unitdate normal="1997/2017" type="inclusive"
							>1997-2017</unitdate></unittitle>
				</did>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Homepage</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>Homepage of the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee. Most other sites in
							this collection are browsable from this page.</p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="1997-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive.org/web/*/http://www.uwm.edu">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture, 1997-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-20174"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/">
						<daodesc>

							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>

						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>UWM Report: News from UW-Milwaukee</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>Homepage of University Communications and Media Relations, the office
							responsible for external communications between UWM and the wider
							community. Included in the capture are press releases, feature stories,
							campus announcements, and back issues of campus publications created by
							University Communications, including the <title render="italic">UWM
								Report</title> (2006-2013); <title render="italic">UWM
								Alumni</title>, formerly <title render="italic">UWM Today</title>
							(2005-2012); <title render="italic">UWM Research Report</title>
							(2009-2012); and <title render="italic">UWM In the News</title>, a
							collection of articles from local media about UWM. As of January 2013,
							links to articles from the "News Archives" and "Features Archives" pages
							are defunct; news releases from 2011 to 2013 may be browsed through the
							main News page.</p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="1997-2017"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/*/http://www.uwm.edu/news">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture, 1997-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>

					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2016"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www5.uwm.edu/news/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2016</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2017"
						href="https://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/https://uwm.edu/news/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
			</c01>
			<c01 id="series2" level="series">
				<did>
					<unittitle>2. Academic and Research Units,
						<unitdate normal="1997/2017">1997-2017</unitdate></unittitle>

				</did>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>College of Engineering and Applied Science</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>Established in 1964, the College of Engineering and Applied Science
							(CEAS) today is organized into five departments of Civil Engineering,
							Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, Industrial and
							Manufacturing Engineering, Materials, and Mechanical Engineering,
							offering both undergraduate and graduate programs in engineering and
							computer science. The College of Engineering and Applied Science site
							contains program information for prospective, incoming, and current
							students; student resources; listings of faculty and administrative
							staff; and news on featured research conducted through CEAS, including
							links to research centers and labs. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2000-2016"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/*/http://www.uwm.edu/CEAS/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture, 2000-2016 </p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/ceas/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2014-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://uwm.edu/engineering/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2014-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>College of Health Sciences</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>The College of Health Sciences is organized into seven departments of
							Biomedical Sciences, Communication Sciences and Disorders, Health
							Informatics and Administration, Kinesiology, Occupational Science and
							Technology, Continuing Education, and Sports and Recreation, offering
							both undergraduate and graduate programs, as well as certificate
							programs. The College of Health Sciences site provides program
							information and resources for future and current students; faculty and
							administrative staff listings and internal resources; College news; and
							links to research labs, clinics, and centers. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2002-2016"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/*/http://www.uwm.edu/chs">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture, 2002-2016</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2014"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/chs/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2014</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2015-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://uwm.edu/healthsciences//">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2015-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>College of Letters and Science</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>The largest of UWM's schools and colleges, the College of Letters and
							Sciences offers traditional liberal arts certificates, undergraduate,
							and graduate degrees provided throughout the 22 humanities, natural
							sciences, and social sciences departments of the College. The College of
							Letters and Sciences site provides information for prospective and
							current students, including material on undergraduate and graduate
							programs, and student services and resources; links to the College of
							Letters and Sciences’ academic departments; resources for faculty and
							staff, including departmental and administrative directories; curriculum
							and governance rules and reports, including assessment plans, budget
							reports, and faculty governance rules; minutes and agendas of the
							Letters and Sciences Faculty Committee; and links to the centers and
							institutes administered by and participating with the College of Letters
							and Sciences, including the Language Resource Center, Center for 21st
							Century Studies, and the Roberto Hernandez Center.</p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="1997-2017"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/*/http://www.uwm.edu/letsci">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture, 1997-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2016"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/letsci/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2016</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2016-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://uwm.edu/letters-science/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2016-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>College of Nursing</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>Established in 1965, the UWM College of Nursing is Wisconsin’s largest
							nursing school and only one of two schools that offer a full complement
							of degree options including Bachelor of Science, Master of Nursing,
							Doctor of Nursing Practice, PhD, and graduate certificates. The College
							of Nursing site includes information for undergraduate and graduate
							students, including program details, forms and materials, and student
							resources; faculty and staff directories; faculty research areas and
							actively funded research projects, with links to the College’s research
							centers and institutes; and resources on community and corporate
							partners of the College. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2002-2016"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/*/http://www.uwm.edu/nursing">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture, 2002-2016</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/nursing/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>

				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Graduate School</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>The UWM Graduate School awards advanced academic degrees to graduate
							students who have previously earned bachelor’s degrees through
							undergraduate programs at UWM and elsewhere. The site includes relevant
							information for prospective, incoming, and current students; faculty and
							staff resources; academic policies and procedures; and extensive
							information on research conducted through the Graduate School. Minutes
							and agendas are also available for Graduate School committees including
							the Graduate Course and Curriculum Committee, the Graduate Fellowships
							Committee, and the Graduate Program Review Committee. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="1997-2016"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/*/http://www.uwm.edu/Dept/Grad_Sch/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture, 1997-2016</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2016"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www.graduateschool.uwm.edu/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2016</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2016-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http:/uwm.edu/graduateschool/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2016-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Helen Bader School of Social Welfare</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>the Helen Bader School of Social Welfare offers undergraduate and
							graduate degrees to prepare students for careers in social, health,
							educational, and criminal justice professions. The site includes
							information for future and current students, including policies and
							procedures, and student resources; a faculty and staff directory;
							research resources, including links to research conducted within and in
							conjunction with the School; and news and events within the School. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="1997-2016"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/*/http://www.uwm.edu/Dept/SSW/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture (As School of Social Welfare), 1997-2016</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2015"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/hbssw/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2015</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2015-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://uwm.edu/socialwelfare/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2015-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Joseph J. Zilber School of Public Health</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>the Zilber School of Public Health advances the understanding of health
							disparities, educates the local public health workforce, guides public
							health policy, and partners with local organizations to address
							community public health issues. The site includes information about the
							School’s certificate, master’s, and doctoral degree programs; faculty
							and staff listings; information on the School of Public Health Planning
							Council, including a listing of council members, executive summary, and
							full report; rosters of numerous teams and committees, including the
							Epidemiology PhD Work Team, School Formation Planning Committee, and the
							Library Resources Committee among others; and news on research
							initiatives, including links to the School’s laboratories. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/publichealth/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://uwm.edu/publichealth/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Peck School of the Arts</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>Home Page for the UWM Peck School of the Arts, including academic
							information about the school and its constitutent departments. Also
							included is information about admissions criteria, press releases, and a
							calendar of events staged by PSOA students, faculty, and guest artists.
						</p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="1997-2015"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/19971016104210/http://www.uwm.edu/Dept/SFA/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Wayback Machine Capture (as School of Fine Arts), 1997-2015</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2014"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/19971016104210/http://www.uwm.edu/Dept/SFA/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Wayback Machine Capture (as School of Fine Arts), 1997-2015</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2014"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/psoa/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2014</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2015-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://uwm.edu/arts">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2015-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2015-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://uwm.edu/arts">
						<daodesc>
							<p>2015-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Research Centers and Institutes</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>As a Research I designated university, UWM encompasses a network of
							clinics, centers, institutes, and laboratories to accommodate the
							research needs of faculty, entrepreneurs, scientists, and graduate
							students. The UWM Centers and Institutes' site includes links for
							numerous centers and institutes, including the Center for Celtic
							Studies; the Institute on Race and Ethnicity; the Roberto Hernandez
							Center; and the Institute for Visual Arts (INOVA).</p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2014"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/academics/centers-institutes.cfm">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2014</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>School of Architecture and Urban Planning</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>Established in 1966, the School of Architecture and Urban Planning
							(SARUP) offers Bachelor’s, Master’s and Doctoral degrees in
							Architecture, a Master’s in Urban Planning, a Coordinated Master’s
							degree in Architecture and Urban Planning, and numerous certificate
							programs. The School of Architecture and Urban Planning site includes
							materials about the School’s programs; faculty and staff directories;
							galleries of student and faculty work; and news and events, including
							the School’s lecture series and exhibitions. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2000-2017"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/*/http://www.uwm.edu/SARUP/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture, 2000-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao><dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/SARUP/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>School of Freshwater Sciences</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>Established in 2009, the School of Freshwater Sciences (SFS) is the first
							graduate school in the United States dedicated solely to the study of
							freshwater and offers research and education programs in freshwater
							system dynamics; human and ecosystem health; freshwater technology; and
							freshwater economics, policy, and management. The School of Freshwater
							Sciences site offers course descriptions and information on master's and
							doctoral degree programs; news and events; faculty and administrative
							staff listings; information on the School's fleet and facilities; and
							news on research conducted through SFS.</p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/freshwater/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>School of Information Studies</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>Established in 1966, the School of Information Studies (SOIS) offers
							undergraduate and graduate degree programs that prepare students for
							careers in the information professions. The School of Information
							Studies site includes information for prospective and current students,
							including program materials, course descriptions, student resources, and
							links to student services; faculty and administration directories; links
							to SOIS social media sites; information on student and professional
							organizations and chapters; and notes on research conducted through the
							School, including faculty and student interests and funded research,
							workshop and funding resources, and links to the School’s research
							centers and groups. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="1997-2016"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/*/http://www.uwm.edu/Dept/SLIS/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture (As School of Library and Information Studies), 1997-2016</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao><dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2014"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/sois/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2014</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2016-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://uwm.edu/informationstudies/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2016-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2016-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://uwm.edu/informationstudies/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>2016-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Sheldon B. Lubar School of Business</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>The AACSB accredited Lubar School of Business provides undergraduate and
							graduate business programs, including the nationally ranked MBA program.
							The Lubar School of Business site includes information for prospective,
							incoming, and current students; faculty and administrative staff
							listings; news and events; and links to the School’s research centers,
							including the Center for Technological Innovation, the Helen Bader
							Institute for Nonprofit Management, and the Bostrom Center for
							Entrepreneurship and Innovation among others. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2001-2011"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/20010405132048/http://www.uwm.edu/Dept/Business/index.html">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture (As School of Business Administration), 2001-2011</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/business/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>

				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>UWM Libraries</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>The UWM Libraries, formerly the UWM Golda Meir Library, accommodates the
							information needs of UWM faculty and students through traditional print
							and electronic resources and unique materials available through library
							departments. The site includes general information about the Libraries,
							including library policies, services, and staff directory; information
							on the Daniel M. Soref Learning Commons, including available services
							and policies; and links to the departments of the Libraries and the
							Friends of the Golda Meir Library. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="1997-2016"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/*/http://www.uwm.edu/Library/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture, 1997-2016</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/libraries/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>

				</c02>
			</c01>
			<c01 id="series3" level="series">
				<did>
					<unittitle>3. Administrative Units, <unitdate normal="1997/2017">1997-2017</unitdate></unittitle>
				</did>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Academic Affairs</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>The Provost’s Office is responsible for the administration of academic
							affairs of the university and renders decisions on academic programming,
							including curricula changes; the establishment and termination of degree
							programs; budget decisions in the academic sector; and long-range
							planning for academic affairs. The site includes policies and procedures
							for academic program planning and review; reports and assessments of the
							Access to Success initiative, the campus blueprint to enhance access to
							UWM and increase student success; budget and planning reports and
							proposals; student Factbooks and entrance/exit surveys; and resources on
							UWM’s diversity action initiatives. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="1997-2016"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/*/http://www.uwm.edu/Dept/Acad_Aff/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture, 1997-2016</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2015"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/acad_aff/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2015</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2015-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://uwm.edu/academicaffairs/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2015-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Alumni Association</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>The UWM Alumni Association provides services for graduates of UWM and its
							predecessor institutions, including volunteering and networking
							opportunities; career counseling through Alumni Career Services; and the
							Alumni Association's publication, <title render="italic">UWM
								Today</title>. The site includes news on Alumni events; access to
							Alumni Association publications, including back issues of the UWM alumni
							magazine; and information on the various Alumni chapters.</p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="1999-2017"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/20010424023134/http://www.uwm.edu/Org/Alumni/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture, 1999-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2014"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/alumni/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2014</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2014-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://uwm.edu/alumni/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2014-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Auxiliary Services</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>The Auxiliary Services department provides support for UWM in regards to
							Restaurant Operations, Computer Operations, and the Center for Student
							Involvement. The site includes resources for UWM Panther Card and
							ePanther Accounts and links to departmental sites, including the UWM
							Bookstore; the Student Union; Neighborhood and University Housing;
							Restaurant Operations; Reservations and Event Planning Services; and the
							Student Association. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2014"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www.aux.uwm.edu/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2014</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2014-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://uwm.edu/auxiliaryservices/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2014-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Campus Budget Site</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>Web Resources created by the Office of the Chancellor, University
							Relations, and Finance and Administrative Affairs, to collect
							information about developments surrounding WI Act 10 (2011), WI Act 55
							(2015), and the effects of the $250M cut to the UW System.</p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://uwm.edu/budget">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Finance and Administrative Affairs</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>Finance and Administrative Affairs provides accounting, budgetary,
							personnel, IT, and other operational services for UWM. The site includes
							personnel and IT related policies and procedures, university weather and
							emergency operations procedures, and links to the individual departments
							of the Division of Finance and Administrative Affairs.</p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2009-2016"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/20111001001259/http://www4.uwm.edu/faa/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture, 2009-2016</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2014"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/faa/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2014</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Office of the Chancellor</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>The chancellor is the chief administrative officer for the university,
							with responsibility for overseeing UWM's administrative offices,
							centers, colleges, and schools. The site includes an up-to-date listing
							of campus leadership; communications from current Chancellor Mark Mone,
							including his Plenary Address and Regent Address; and links to UWM
							initiatives, including Access to Success, the Wisconsin Energy Resource
							Consortium, the Greater Milwaukee Foundation, and the Research Growth
							Initiative, among others. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="Office of the Chancellor"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/*/http://www.uwm.edu/Dept/Chancellor/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture, 1998-2010</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="Office of the Chancellor"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/chancellor/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Secretary of the University</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>The Secretary of the University manages and facilitates governance
							documents at UWM, including university-wide policies and procedures and
							minutes/agendas of standing and ad hoc faculty and academic staff
							committees. Minutes and agendas for the Faculty Senate and Academic
							Staff Senate can be found on this site, as well as Faculty Documents,
							which are reports and proposals produced by committees and departments
							for consideration and/or approval by the Faculty Senate.</p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="1998-2009"
						href="http://wayback.archive.org/web/20100715000000*/http://www.uwm.edu/Dept/SecU/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Wayback Machine Capture, 1998-2009</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2009-2012"
						href="http://wayback.archive.org/web/20090401000000*/http://www.uwm.edu/secu">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2009-2012</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2016"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/secu/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2016</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Student Affairs</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>The Division of Student Affairs comprises of several units, which provide
							programs and services that support the personal and professional
							development of UWM students throughout their university careers.
							Divisional Units of the UWM Division of Student Affairs include the
							Career Development Center, Center for Student Involvement, the
							Children’s Center, the LGBT Resource Center, and Women’s Resource Center
							among others. The site includes general information, including campus
							maps, listings of campus programs and events, and Student Affairs
							directories; links to the Center for Student Involvement; and
							information regarding the Student Affairs Assessment Team. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www.aux.uwm.edu/studentaffairs/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>University Relations</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>The Division of University Relations at UWM encompasses several areas,
							including university communications and media relations, government
							relations, and neighborhood relations. The site includes links to the
							aforementioned divisional units; information pertaining to public
							records requests; and the Final Campus Master Plan report, completed in
							May 2010. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2014"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www4.uwm.edu/univ_rel/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2014</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2014-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://uwm.edu/universityrelations/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2014-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
			</c01>
			<c01 id="series4" level="series">
				<did>
					<unittitle>4. Athletics, <unitdate normal="2000/2017">2000-2017</unitdate></unittitle>
				</did>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>UWM Panthers</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>The UWM Athletics site includes materials for all men’s and women’s
							sports, including current rosters, statistics, schedules and results,
							media guides, and news. Archived rosters, statistics, news, and media
							guides are available for all sports as well. The site also provides
							materials on the athletic department in general, including a staff
							directory, facilities information, a UWM Athletics Hall of Fame, and
							department news. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2000-2016"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/*/http://uwmpanthers.fansonly.com/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture, 2000-2016</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2007-2016"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/*/http://uwmpanthers.cstv.com/index-main.html">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Internet Archive Capture, 2007-2016</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao><dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2014"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www.uwmpanthers.com/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2014</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2014-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://mkepanthers.com//">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2014-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
			</c01>
			<c01 id="series5" level="series">
				<did>
					<unittitle>5. Social Media Accounts, <unitdate normal="2009/2017">2009-2017</unitdate></unittitle>
				</did>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Facebook</unittitle>
					</did>
					<c03>
						<did>
							<unittitle>Main UWM Account</unittitle>
						</did>
						<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2017"
							href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www.facebook.com/UWMilwaukee/">
							<daodesc>
								<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
							</daodesc>
						</dao>
					</c03>
					<c03>
						<did>
							<unittitle>Milwaukee Panthers</unittitle>
						</did>
						<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2017"
							href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www.facebook.com/MilwaukeePanthers/">
							<daodesc>
								<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
							</daodesc>
						</dao>
					</c03>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Flickr</unittitle>
					</did>
					<c03>
						<did>
							<unittitle>Main UWM Account</unittitle>
						</did>
						<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2017"
							href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www.flickr.com/photos/uwmilwaukee/">
							<daodesc>
								<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
							</daodesc>
						</dao>
					</c03>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Twitter</unittitle>
					</did>
					<c03>
						<did>
							<unittitle>Main UWM Account</unittitle>
						</did>
						<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2017"
							href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://twitter.com/uwm/">
							<daodesc>
								<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
							</daodesc>
						</dao>
					</c03>
					<c03>
						<did>
							<unittitle>Milwaukee Panthers</unittitle>
						</did>
						<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2009-2017"
							href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://twitter.com/MKEPanthers/">
							<daodesc>
								<p>Archive-It Capture, 2009-2017</p>
							</daodesc>
						</dao>
					</c03>
					<c03>
						<did>
							<unittitle>UWM Alumni Association</unittitle>
						</did>
						<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2017"
							href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://twitter.com/uwmalumni/">
							<daodesc>
								<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
							</daodesc>
						</dao>
					</c03>
				</c02>
			</c01>
			<c01 id="series6" level="series">
				<did>
					<unittitle>6. UWM Affiliate Sites, <unitdate normal="2012/2017">2012-2017</unitdate></unittitle>
				</did>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>Media Milwaukee</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>An ongoing journalism and mass media project, sponsored by the UWM Dept.
							of Journalism and Media Studies, focusing on local news in Milwaukee and
							around the UWM campus. It includes stories about events and students on
							campus, as well as local sports and opinions. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2014-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www.uwmfdn.org/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2014-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>UWM Foundation</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent>
						<p>The Mission of the UWM Foundation is to support the educational, literary
							and scientific endeavors of the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee by
							receiving, managing and distributing gifts to benefit the University's
							students, faculty, programs and community. Included on the site are a
							news feed, staffing information, and financial reports. </p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new" title="2012-2017"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://www.uwmfdn.org/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
				<c02 level="subseries">
					<did>
						<unittitle>UWM Post</unittitle>
					</did>
					<scopecontent id="ref122">
						<p>Website of the UWM Post, the online-only student newspaper organization
							for the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee. The site includes both
							UWM-specific original reporting and links to UWM and Milwaukee news from
							other news outlets around the city.</p>
					</scopecontent>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new"
						href="http://web.archive.org/web/*/http://www.uwmpost.com">
							<p>Internet Archive Capture, 1999-2016</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
					<dao actuate="onrequest" show="new"
						href="http://wayback.archive-it.org/3368/*/http://uwmpost.com/">
						<daodesc>
							<p>Archive-It Capture, 2012-2017</p>
						</daodesc>
					</dao>
				</c02>
			</c01>
		</dsc>
	</archdesc>
</ead>
